{
    "subject": "resource/James_Dyrenforth",
    "predicate": "property/shortDescription",
    "object": "American actor",
    "human_readable": "James Dyrenforth is an American actor.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9663315415382385,
            "question": "Is James Dyrenforth a well-known actor?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9319997429847717,
            "question": "Is James Dyrenforth known for acting?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8750022649765015,
            "question": "What are some of James Dyrenforth's notable roles?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8551664352416992,
            "question": "What country is James Dyrenforth an actor in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7616060972213745,
            "question": "What is James Dyrenforth known for besides acting?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7364225387573242,
            "question": "Has James Dyrenforth appeared in any movies?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6877533793449402,
            "question": "What profession does James Dyrenforth have?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6872836947441101,
            "question": "What nationality is James Dyrenforth?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6563664674758911,
            "question": "Where is James Dyrenforth from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5762104988098145,
            "question": "Has James Dyrenforth won any awards for his acting?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=James Dyrenforth is an American actor.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1491_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where is James Dyrenforth from?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1491_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What nationality is James Dyrenforth?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1491_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What profession does James Dyrenforth have?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1491_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1491_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1491_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1491_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1491_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1491_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1491_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1491_53.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1491_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1491_57.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1491_74.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about James Dyrenforth's career as an actor, including his roles and the years in which he appeared in films. This supports the statement that James Dyrenforth is an American actor."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "James Dyrenforth was born in Chicago, Illinois, USA.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}